PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hardworking and well-rounded professional with experience in various fields, including business administration, education, and technology. Successful history of leadership and recruiting responsible execution of assigned tasks, and eagerness to learn. Proven ability to implement creative solutions and meet objectives.

EXPERIENCE

Spectrum Staffing Solutions, Philadelphia, PA - Assistant Manager

June 2018 - PRESENT

- Assist in day to day operations of a multi-million staffing agency including management of staff, recruiting, data entry, and bookkeeping
- Lead a team of staffed employees by ensuring responsibilities are met and providing mentorship as needed
- Represent the company in meetings with local schools, healthcare, and businesses to gain contracts
- Evaluate business practices to find and implement ways to improve them

Ridley Park School District, Ridley Park, PA - Personal Care Assistant

May 2017 - Present

- Provide physical, mental, and emotional support to troubled youth within the school district
- Encourage students to remain focused through the use of numerous psychological tactics and patience
- Work with a team of school administrators and staff to follow an IEP plan created to help students succeed

Delaware Business Systems, New Castle, DE - Entry Level Technician

Aug 2014 - Aug 2015

- Deliver technical support to clients experiencing difficulties with devices
- Program and set up POS devices with step by step methods and technical knowledge
- Repair damaged and faulty equipment such as receipt printers, monitors, touchscreens, and computers
- Precisely clean and handle user accessories

EDUCATION

West Chester University, West Chester, PA - Psychology BA

Aug 2014 - Dec 2019

SKILLS

- Leadership
- Willing to Learn
- Video Editing

- Interpersonal
 - Skills
- Problem Solving
- Proficient in Microsoft Apps
- Data Entry